Independent.
Independent networks.
They're a little bit better, but I
would say that we're an example of how
you don't need to be part of a super large company
to be able to do just basic journalism.
All you've got to do is sit and record,
and you'll let the story play out.
And that's why they hate us.
That's why Antifa targets us.
A level of dishonesty that's incredible,
where answers are changed.
Like just before the election, an answer
was changed by Kamala.
She gave a horrible, death-defying, election-defying
answer, and they took the answer out
and they replaced it with another answer
that she gave five minutes later,
having to do with a different subject.
But at least it wasn't election-defying.
No, the level of dishonesty with the media
is incredible, whether it's on Antifa or many
of the other groups.
You're talking about Antifa, and I
know that's close to your heart, because that's the one that's
most affecting you.
But there are others that are as bad or almost as bad
as Antifa, having to do with different people,
different sections of the world.
But it's terrible.
We're not going to let it go on in this country.
We're not going to let it go on.
And a big problem is not all of them,
but some of the networks out there.
And you do wonder why.
You really do?
OK, please.